Last week, my four-year-old daughter, Sally, was invited to a children's party.
上周,我4岁的女儿Sally被邀请去参加一个儿童聚会.
I decided to take her by train.
我决定带她乘火车去.
Sally was very excited because she had never travelled on a train before.
萨莉非常激动,因为她以前从未乘过火车.
She sat near the window and asked questions about everything she saw.
她靠车窗坐着,对她所看到的一切都要问个明白.
Suddenly, a middle-aged lady got on the train and sat opposite Sally.
突然,一个中年妇女上了火车,坐在Sally的对面.
Hello, little girl,' she said.
“你好,小姑娘,”她说.
Sally did not answer, but looked at her curiously.
Sally没回答,却好奇地看着她.
The lady was dressed in a blue coat and a large, funny hat.
那位妇女穿着一件蓝色的大衣,戴着一顶大而滑稽的帽子.
After the train had left the station,
火车开出车站后,
the lady opened her handbag and took out her powder compact.
那位妇女找开了手提包,拿出了她的粉盒.
She then began to make up her face.
然后她开始打扮起来.
Why are you doing that?' Sally asked.
“你为什么要那样做呢?”Sally问.
To make myself beautiful,' the lady answered.
“为了把自己打扮漂亮啊,”那位妇女答道.
She put away her compact and smiled kindly.
她收起来她的粉盒,慈祥地微笑着.
But you are still ugly,' Sally said.
“可是你仍然很难看呀,”萨莉说.
Sally was amused, but I was very embarrassed!
Sally感到很有趣,而我却很尴尬.